《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
我一直忍不住想
I can't help thinking that...
如果我做了不同的事情
if I had done things differently
我和莉娜的关系
with my friendship with Lena,
也许事情会有不同的结果
maybe things would have turned out differently.
你无法知道
There's no way of knowing.
抱歉  我搞不懂
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm confused.
这就是你的全能五维追踪者吗
This is your all-powerful Fifth Dimensional stalker?
不  我不认识他
No. I don't know who this is.
我叫捣蛋鬼先生
I am Mr. Mxyzptlk,
我相信你就是卡拉·丹弗斯
just as I'm sure that you, Kara Danvers,
也是超...
are Su--
进来
Get in here.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我不能再随意进门  得别人邀请才行
I can't just come in anymore. I have to be invited.
快告诉我你是谁  你想干什么
Tell me who you are and what you want, now.
我是你的唯一挚爱  灵魂伴侣
I'm your one true love, your soulmate,
按照孩子们的话来讲就是命中注定
your one true ''pairing'' as the kids say.
我是捣蛋鬼  我爱你  卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Mxyzptlk, and I love you, Kara Zor-El.
你不是吧
Okay. If you...
别来这套
Aw, come on.
如果你是捣蛋鬼  那你为什么长这个样子
If you are Mxy, then why do you look like this?
我只是用了另一副外貌
Okay, I only took on that other form
有魅力的口音来取悦你
and sophisticated accent to impress you.
但是成功了
But it worked.
被你发现了
You caught me.
你耍了我
Tricked me.
没有  我遵循了规矩
No, I followed the rules.
你倒着说了你的名字
You say your name backwards,
你就要回五维空间  没有二话
you go back to the Fifth Dimension, no questions asked.
我想念那头发
Ah, I miss that hair.
真的很想念
I really, really do.
但是现在  我不能用我的超能力
But now, I can't use any of my powers,
除了帮助那些被我捣蛋的人
except to help those whom I have wronged.
真替你难过
Oh, how sad for you.
是的
Yes.
莎士比亚式的悲剧  我同意
A tragedy of Shakespearean proportions, I agree.
但是好消息
But great news.
你是最后一个
You're the last one.
我会需要你的帮助吗
What could I possibly need your help for?
我杀了我哥哥  为了你和我们的朋友
I killed my brother for you, for our friends!
难道你不明白你做了什么吗
Don't you understand what you've done?
你最好的朋友认为她是你的敌人
Your best friend thinks that she is your enemy.
而最糟糕的是
And the worst part...
那是你的错
It's your fault.
你对她隐瞒事实
You hid the truth from her.
你让她从那个虐待狂莱克斯那里知道真相
You let her find out from that sadist, Lex,
现在你觉得
and now, you think
她什么事都可以做得出来
she could be capable of anything.
你到底想说什么
What's your point?
我想说是的这个  亲爱的
My point, toots, is this.
小心点
Careful.
我在给你一次重来的机会
I am offering you a do-over.
我可以送你回到过去
I could send you back in time.
你想不想有个机会亲口告诉莉娜
Wouldn't you like to be able to tell Lena that you're Supergirl
你是超女
on your own terms?
你想不想看看
Wouldn't you like to see...
如果由你主导事情的走向
what the world would look like...
世界会变成什么样
if you controlled the narrative?
你伤她还不够重吗
Haven't you hurt enough?
我懂的
I get it.
你不相信我
You don't trust me.
没事  但这样如何
Okay, but how's this?
准备好了吗  根据五维空间的规定
Ready? Now, by Fifth Dimensional law,
我必须给你这段录音
I am required to give you this recording
内容是我倒着念我名字
of me saying my name backwards,
以防你要把我放逐到五维空间
in case you ever need to banish me to my Fifth Dimension,
-我知道你...  -鬼蛋捣
- which I know that you-- - Kltpzyxm.
我不是坏人
I'm not a villain.
你不该把我当成坏人对待
You shouldn't have treated me like one.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
怎么了
What's going on?
超 女
第五季 第十三集
斯蒂顿匹萨店
你不是真的考虑要做这么做吧
You're not seriously thinking of doing this, are you?
如果我能改变什么呢
What if I could change things?
如果我比莱克斯先一步告诉莉娜我是超女
If I told Lena that I was Supergirl before Lex,
也许她的反应会不一样
maybe she would have reacted differently.
难道这不值得一试吗
I mean, isn't that worth a try?
为了拯救友谊而改变历史吗
Changing history to save a friendship?
卡拉  我不知道  不
Kara, I don't... I don't know. No.
这是为了拯救历史而改变历史
This is changing history to save history,
因为莱克斯和莉娜正在计划干坏事
'cause Lex and Lena are planning something horrible,
我们却毫无头绪
and we are no closer to finding out what that is.
等战斗来袭
And when the fight comes...
我不知道我是否有能力阻止她
I don't know if I have what it takes to stop her.
卡拉
Kara...
你确定你能相信捣蛋鬼吗
are you sure you can trust Mxy?
不能
No.
但是这段录音有用
But the tape recorder worked.
我总是可以用录音把他送走
I... I could always just use it to get him to go away.
听我说
All right, listen to me.
如果你真的认为在莉娜伤害任何人之前
If you really think that this is your best chance
这是你弥补的最好机会
to set things right with Lena before she hurts somebody...
那就放手去做吧
then do it.
好
Okay.
我该怎么做
How do I do this?
天啊
Oh, God.
感谢祖克  你改变主意了
Thank Zook you changed your mind.
没错  我还没改掉偷听的恶习  这是问题
Yes, I'm still working on eavesdropping. That's a problem.
在我们开始之前  捣蛋鬼  我要你保证
Okay, before we do this, Mxy, I need your word
如果事情出了岔子
that if things go sideways,
你会让一切恢复正常
you'll put it all back to normal.
法院下令我必须这么做
I am court-ordered to do so.
小可爱
Boop.
不是看不起超级朋友们
Now, no shade to the Super Friends,
但只有我和试验者时  效果会更好
but it tends to work better when it's just me and the subject.
你们俩有别的计划吗
So, do you two have any plans?
-应该没有  -不不  我们只要
- No. I don't think so. - No. No, we were just gonna--
什么
What...
他们去哪了
Where did they go?
他们在自己的快乐之地
They're in their happy place.
魔法戒律
Magic rules!
游戏开始  丹弗斯
Game on, Danvers!
那好
All right, so,
要怎么做
how does this work?
我会给你看和你人生有关的部分
I will show you relevant parts of your life.
你告诉我什么时候暂停
You'll tell me when to pause,
我会打个响指
I will snap,
就像这样
like thus,
送你回去
sending you back.
你会改变历史
You will change history.
一旦你把真相告诉莉娜后  你就会回来
Once you have confronted Lena, you will come back,
我们会在你阁楼的沙发上安全地看着你
we will watch from your loft and the safety of your couch.
如果你对多米诺连锁反效应觉得满意的话
If you are comfortable with the domino effect...
我会再打个响指
I will then snap again,
而这时
at which point,
那就会变成现实
it will become reality.
-好吗  -好
- Okay? - Okay.
那么三年的友情  到底是哪里出错了
So, three years of friendship. Where did it go wrong?
这个嘛
Well...
当莉娜和我说她知道我是超女时
When Lena told me that she knew I was Supergirl,
-她非常生气  -嗯
- she was furious. - Yeah.
她说我当她是傻子
She said I made a fool out of her.
她觉得很耻辱
She was humiliated.
所以我们要找的是
Okay, so, we're looking for a moment
你让你最好的朋友
where you made your best friend
觉得自己是个大白痴的那一刻  对吧
feel like a big, dumb idiot. Yeah?
-真直截  -好
- In so many words. - Okay.
羞辱的一刻开始播放
Well, we have an embarrassment of riches.
系好安全带  我来让飞机着陆
Get your seatbelt back on. I'm gonna land this plane.
装得还挺像
Oh, yeah, this is a good one. Oh.
卡拉  卡拉
Kara? Kara?
老天  我讨厌飞行
God, I hate flying.
太糟糕了
Oh! Ugh. This is awful!
-我太糟糕了  -你太糟糕了
- I'm awful! - You're awful.
我只是同意你的说法  换我肯定不那么说
I was just agreeing with you. I would never say that.
行
Okay.
回到仁慈袭击之前
Let's go to before Mercy attacks.
-就那里吗  -嗯
- Right there? - Mmm-hmm.
-确定吗  -确定
- You sure? - Yes.
别搞砸了
Don't mess it up.
说实话  我一开始就不怎么信任那些政客们
To be honest, I didn't have much faith in politicians to begin with.
我觉得他们都不可信
I just don't think any of them can be trusted.
别这么震惊  卡拉
Don't look so scandalized, Kara.
你知道的  我有多愤世嫉俗
You know how cynical I can be.
你没事吧
Is everything okay?
你不必这么愤世嫉俗
You shouldn't have to be so cynical.
你为人善良正直
You're good and righteous,
只...只可惜
and... and the tragedy is,
这世界让你变得愤世嫉俗
the world has made you cynical
因为你经历了太多背叛
because you've been betrayed so many times.
被你母亲  你哥哥
By your mother, by your brother...
现在又被我背叛
and now, by me.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我不是你想象的那样
I'm not who you think I am.
我是超女
I'm Supergirl.
我从来没想过骗你
I never meant to deceive you.
只是不知道怎么开口
I just didn't know how to tell you.
你在这待着  我去解决
You stay here. I'll deal with this.
莉娜
Lena?
怎么回事  她去哪了
What happened? Where'd she go?
事情换了一种方式展开
Ah. Events are unfolding differently now.
天啊  我得赶上变化
Oh, boy. Um, I need to catch up.
她在那里
Ah, there she is.
她去大都会了
She went to Metropolis.
我的天
Oh, my God.
她去见小萨了
She went to see Sam.
所以  卡拉就是超女
So, Kara is Supergirl?
是的  我头有点晕
Yeah, I know. My head's kind of spinning.
你是主宰的时候  我制造氪石阻止你
When you were Reign, and I made Kryptonite to stop you...
超女的反应那么激烈
You know, in response, Supergirl was so horrible.
卡拉却还是一样
And then, Kara was the same.
心地善良  支持我
She was so kind and supportive.
但我在想  究竟哪个才是真的卡拉
But it made me think, which was the real Kara?
如果真正的卡拉认为我是坏人
And if the real Kara thought I was a villain...
那我可能真的是坏人吧
then maybe that's all I really am.
不  莉娜  你怎么能这么想
No, Lena, no. How could you ever think that?
莉娜  你制作氪石将我和主宰分离
Lena, you made Kryptonite to split me from Reign
救了我的命
and to save my life.
你从来都不是坏人
You were never the villain.
你一直是英雄
You were always the hero.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很需要你这番话
I really needed to hear that.
这个时间线的莉娜可能永远不会原谅我
The Lena in this timeline might never forgive me.
可能还会恨我
She might even hate me.
你知道吗  你知道吗
You know what? You know what?
要是小萨阻止她走上邪路
If Sam stops her from going down a dark path,
我能接受
I can live with that.
但你不能
Except you literally can't.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的天
Oh, my God.
这是自由代表向空气里投放氪石的那晚
This is the night Agent Liberty poisoned the air with Kryptonite.
要我说  我们还是关了吧
You know what? Maybe we should shut this off.
不不不
No, no, no.
莉娜救过我一次
Lena saved me the first time.
虽然恨我  但她还是会救我的
She might hate me, but she'll save me again.
即使她想也来不及
She wants to, but she'll never make it in time.
警告
卡拉·丹弗斯  卒于2018年10月
卡拉
Hey, Kara.
抱歉  感恩节我没来
I'm sorry I missed Thanksgiving.
我们...我们没有你就手足无措
We're just... We're so lost without you.
我
I...
没有你就手足无措
am so lost without you.
迟到的感恩节快乐
Happy late Thanksgiving.
你能关掉吗
Can you please turn it off?
我不想看了  关掉
I can't watch any more of this. Just stop it!
太糟糕了
That was horrible.
显然  你不想一直死去
Obviously, you don't want to stay dead.
不  不
No! No!
不  我要回到更早的时候
No, I have to go back further.
我明白了
I get it now.
我的双重身份让莉娜以为
My dual identities made Lena think
她不能相信任何一面的我
that she couldn't trust either side of me.
我是个伪君子
I was a hypocrite.
那么  这次跟氪石有关的对话
Okay, so, when exactly did this Kryptonite-fueled
究竟发生在什么时候
tete-a-tete happen?
是在...是在
It was... It was, uh,
我们发现莉娜藏匿了主宰之后
just after we found out lena was housing Reign.
超女
莉娜  灭世者要来了
Lena, the Worldkillers are coming.
我们得带你去安全的地方
We have to get you someplace-- Mmm...
快进  快进
Skip forward. Skip.
你绝对不能再制造氪石
You are never going to make Kryptonite ever again.
-你真的有上帝情结  -看  就是这里
- You really do have a God-complex. - See, there.
-我要阻止的就是这场争吵  -嗯  行
- This fight is what I'm trying to avoid. -Mmm-hmm. Okay.
倒带
So, go back.
我需要你查清楚是不是真的没有氪石了
I need you to find out if there really isn't any Kryptonite left.
卡拉  你这是要我
Kara, you're asking me
背叛一个我很在乎的人
to betray somebody that I really care about.
我不该那么做的
I never should have done that.
-必须在这之前  -好  稍等  这之前
- Uh, yeah, it has to be before this. - Yeah, hang on, before.
得再往前一点
We have to go back further.
-停  -好
- Here. - Yep.
我朋友找我求助
My friend came to me.
她感到孤单害怕  我必须想办法帮她
She was alone and afraid. I had to do something.
我要你跟我说实话
I need you to level with me.
你手上还有氪石吗
Do you have any more Kryptonite?
-就是这里  -嗯
- This is it. - Mmm-hmm.
莉娜就是从这里开始不信任超女的
This is the moment that Lena started to distrust Supergirl.
我要在这里跟她坦白  所以...
This is when I have to tell her, so... Okay.
点亮我吧  捣蛋鬼
Beam me up, Mxy.
没有特别的口号吗
You don't have a catchphrase?
到时候再想好了
We'll work on that.
"女性之力"  算了
''Girl power!'' No.
我朋友找我求助
My friend came to me.
她感到孤单害怕  我必须想办法帮她
She was alone and afraid. I had to do something.
这种即使不顾全世界的看法
That feeling of needing to protect your friend,
也一定要保护朋友的感觉
no matter what the world thinks...
我比你更能体会
I understand that more than you know.
你曾经跟我说
You once told me
卡拉·丹弗斯是你的英雄
Kara Danvers was your hero.
我没跟你说过  我是跟...
I never told you that. I told...
是我  莉娜
It's me, Lena.
我一直都是卡拉
I've always been Kara.
卡拉  你怎么能这样
Kara, how could you?
抱歉  没有早点告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
三周前  我发现小萨  我最好的朋友之一
Three weeks ago, I found out that Sam, one of my closest friends,
是杀人如麻的氪星人
was a homicidal Kryptonian.
我独自经历了这可怕的一切
I went through that terror alone.
我每天拿着生命在冒险
I risked my life day after day for weeks
因为我以为只能靠我
because I believed that I was the only one
一个人保护她  拯救她了
who could be trusted to protect her, to save her.
你原本可以帮我的
I could have used your help.
如果你早点告诉我真相
I would have used your help
我就可以让你帮我
if you'd bothered to tell me the truth before now.
如果你当初信任我
If you'd trusted me then,
我就不必独自面对危险了
I wouldn't have had to go through that danger alone!
对不起
I'm so sorry,
但我以为我是在保护你
but I thought I was protecting you.
但是现在我们可以冰释前嫌  一起合作了
But now, we can... we can move past it and work as partners.
你觉得这一切之后我还能跟你合作吗
You expect me to be your partner after this?
你所做的一切都证明了
When all you've done is prove to me
我不能信任你
that you can't be trusted at all?
糟了
Oh, no.
我
I...
-我忘了  -好吧
- I forgot. - Yeah.
灭世者那天引起了月食
The Worldkiller started an eclipse that day.
所以  你忘记了  月食
So, you forgot the... forgot the eclipse...
也忘记了氪石炸弹
...and then, you also forgot the Kryptonite bomb.
你知道这教会了我什么吗
You know what we're not gonna do?
就是我们绝对不能依靠你的记忆了
We're not gonna rely on your memory anymore
尤其是这种重要的细节
for maybe, like, big, important details.
我就那么一说
Just sayin'.
我们再找其他地方
We got to try something else.
-比如这里  -别  先看看后面的情节
- How about here? - No! No. Just let this play out a bit,
因为在原版的情节中
because in the original version of events...
莉娜帮助我和超查部抗击了灭世者
...Lena helped me and the DEO to fight the Worldkillers.
-好吧  -我知道她现在很生气
- Okay. - I know she's upset right now,
但是她会帮我们的
but she's gonna help us.
欢迎来到最疯狂的一个版本
Welcome to the bizarro version
那就是她不帮助超查部
where she does not help the DEO,
-就是现在  -什么
- right... right here. - What?
天哪  不要
Oh, God! No.
如果莉娜不帮我们抗击灭世者  那...
If Lena doesn't help us fight the Worldkillers, then-- Yep.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
等等  你跳过了很多
Wait. You're skipping a lot!
这都是在不断展开  情节好多
This is all exposition, so much exposition.
等等  那是蒙·艾尔吗
Hold on! Was that Mon-El?
对
Yes.
-他没回到未来吗  -没有
- So, he didn't go back to the future? - No.
原来如此
Huh. Of course.
如果我们没打败瘟疫
If we didn't defeat Pestilence,
那他就会跟我们一起
then he would have been there with us...
去小萨妈妈家
...when we went to Sam's mom's house.
你能把我扔进去吗
Can you... Can you snap me in there?
我想知道他是怎么看的
I want to get his perspective.
我一直不理解他哪点吸引了你
I never understood what you saw in him.
为了你自己的安全  最好离开吧
You need to leave for your own safety.
我不会丢下我女儿
I... I won't leave my daughter.
她小时候我让她失望了
I failed her when she was a girl.
我不会再让她失望的
I refuse to fail her again.
那你有没有安全的地方可以藏起来
Well, is there at least a safe place for you to hide?
有个安全房间
There's a safe room.
我在那里等
I'll wait there.
-我们应该采取防守姿势  -等等
- We should take up defensive positions. - No, wait. Um...
我需要你的建议
I need your advice.
我最后终于告诉莉娜我是超女了
I finally told Lena I'm Supergirl.
她反应如何
How... How did she take it?
不太好
Not well.
我也不怪她
And I don't blame her.
我本来应该是她最好的朋友
I mean, I'm supposed to be her best friend,
我却骗了她
and I... I lied
而且像她生命中其他人一样背叛了她
and betrayed her just like everyone else in her life has.
我该怎么办
So, what do I do?
其实  我和莉娜有很多共同点
You know, Lena and I have a lot in common.
我们都被家人背叛
We've both been betrayed by our own families.
所以当本该最爱我们的人
And when the people who are supposed to love you the most
让我们失望  会让一个人觉得...
let you down, it just makes you feel so...
非常脆弱  你懂吗
so vulnerable, you know?
但我妈妈和卢瑟一家
But my mother and the Luthors,
他们背叛莉娜是出于自私
they betrayed Lena for their own selfish reasons.
他们
They...
他们是想要利用她
They wanted to take advantage of her.
你撒谎是为了保护她
You lied to... to protect her.
因为她是你的朋友
Because she's your friend.
我知道莉娜现在很受伤  但是...
Now, I know Lena's hurting right now, but...
等她想明白这一点
once she understands that...
她会原谅你的
she'll forgive you.
借你吉言
I hope you're right.
但我觉得我没办法原谅我自己
But I don't think I'll ever be able to forgive myself.
你知道犯错是可以的吧
You know it's okay to mess up, right?
不管我犯过多少错  你总是原谅我
No matter how many mistakes I've made, you've always forgiven me.
你应该知道  你也值得拥有
You should, uh, know that you deserve the same compassion
你给予他人的同理心
that you show others.
主宰马上就来了  我们得准备好
Reign will be here soon. We should get ready.
想我了吗
Did you miss me?
小萨  小萨  这不是你
Sam! Sam, no, this isn't you!
我知道你还在里面  我知道
I know you're in there, I know you are!
不要
No.
你还真以为你能阻止我  超女
You really thought you could stop me, Supergirl?
-你连这一个可悲的人类都保护不了  -小萨
- You can't even protect this one pathetic human. - Oh, Sam...
但我可以
But I can.
因为这是我用来
Because this is the tool
唤醒主宰  让你湮灭的工具
I use to bring Reign out and bury you down.
回来找我们吧  小萨
Come back to us, Sam!
我会杀掉...
I will kill...
你们所有人
you all!
你不会
No, you won't.
小萨  小萨
Sam! Sam!
莉娜
Lena.
怎么回事
What happened?
小萨  没事的  你没事了
Sam, it's okay. It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
小萨  对不起
Oh, Sam, I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
你做到了
You did it!
你救了小萨
You saved Sam.
是啊  而且没有用氪石的帮助
Yeah, and I did it without Kryptonite.
不
No!
愚蠢
Fool!
我是灭世者
I am a Worldkiller.
没有人可以阻止我
And I cannot be stopped!
不
No!
小萨  不  不要  小萨
Sam! No! No! No! Sam!
不要
No, please!
回来  小萨
Come back to me, Sam!
捣蛋鬼  他们全死了
Mxy, they're all dead.
让我出去
Please, get me out of here.
莉娜生气不是因为伪善
Lena was never angry about hypocrisy.
而是因为我没有一开始就跟她说清楚
She was angry because I never shared my identity
我到底是谁
with her in the first place.
你知道这是什么意思吗
So, you know what that means?
我们得回到最开始
We have to go back to the very beginning.
给我日期和时间  我帮你实现
Give me a date and a time, I will make it so.
我想想
Let me think. Uh...
等等
Hang on a second.
还在缓冲
It's just, it's buffering.
捣蛋鬼电视台
有时候会出现这种情况
This happens sometimes.
多次元无线网络信号不好
It's the interdimensional Wi-Fi.
算了  不管这个了
You know what? It doesn't even matter.
你们整个友谊我都在β捣蛋鬼上存了
I've got your entire friendship on BetaMyx.
你们是什么时候成为朋友的
So, when did the two of you become friends?
莉娜搬到纳新诺市
莉莉安承认爱莉娜
超女和莉娜打败纳米机器人
好像是...
It... It was...
莉娜搬来纳新诺市之后
Right after Lena moved to National City.
你们一起经历了好多
You have had a lot of adventures.
请叫莉娜
"Lena," please.
能再见到你真好  丹弗斯女士
It's good to see you again, Miss Danvers.
-要是我叫你莉娜  -那我就叫你卡拉...
- If I'm calling you "Lena"... - Kara--
-太...  -怎么了吗
- Oh, it's too... - Anything?
-太早了  -太早了
- Too soon. - Too soon.
我写过一篇严厉斥责你们设备的文章
I wrote a scathing article about your device.
快到了  这里
Mmm... Getting closer. Here.
我希望你把这些邮件给我
I would hate for you to give me these emails
不是因为你有我们可以当朋友的错觉
out of some misplaced sense of friendship.
就在这之后我和莉娜成为了真正的朋友
This was right before Lena and I really became friends.
看  她要说了
See, she's about to say,
我不是来交朋友的
I didn't come here to make friends.
她不想向别人敞开心怀
She didn't wanna let anyone in,
然后  当她敞开心怀时
and then, when she did,
我却犯错了  没向她敞开心怀
I made the mistake of not letting her in, too.
这一次  我要做出正确的选择
This time, I'm gonna do it right.
再见
Bye!
我不是来交朋友的
I didn't come here to make friends.
我想告诉你件事
I wanna show you something.
听着  我真的很忙  所以如果我们能...
Listen, I'm really busy, so, if we could just--
是你
It's you.
-卡拉·丹佛斯是超女  -是的
- Kara Danvers is Supergirl. - Yeah.
真不敢相信我被一双眼镜骗到了
Can't believe I was fooled by a pair of glasses.
别上心  很多人都是
Don't worry, a lot people are.
天啊  我得召回那些外星人侦测装置
Oh, God, I have to recall all those alien detection devices
因为它们显然没起作用
'cause they clearly don't work.
你不生气吗
You're not angry?
不  太厉害了
No, it's incredible.
我是说  太厉害了
I mean, you're incredible!
但是
But...
你为什么告诉我这么大的一个秘密
Why are you trusting me with such a big secret?
你跟我没那么熟
You barely know me.
因为我知道你最想做的
Because I know that what you want more than anything
就是做好事
is to do good.
我也知道你很难相信别人
And I know it's hard for you to trust people,
但我现在得告诉你  我毫无保留地
but I need you to know now, without a doubt,
信任你
I trust you.
我的堂弟  你的哥哥  他们都错了
My cousin, your brother, they got it wrong.
试想我们联手能做到什么
Imagine what we could do together.
卢瑟家族和超人家族的人  一起组队
A Luthor and a Super, working together as a team.
我们如果搭档  可以改变世界
If we were partners, we could change the world.
仅仅在宣布组成搭档后的一个月
Only months after publicly declaring their partnership,
超女与莉娜·卢瑟揭露外星人武器黑市
超女和莉娜·卢瑟组成的无敌组合
the formidable duo of Supergirl and Lena Luthor
已经扫除了纳欣诺市的犯罪
has already cleaned up National City's criminal element.
超女与莉娜·卢瑟颠覆美杜莎病毒散播阴谋
这对组合真的所向披靡
This pair is literally unstoppable!
还具有时尚感
Not to mention, fashionable
超女换发后  刘海需求创新高
尤其是在莉娜说服超女剪掉钢铁之发
after Lena convinced Supergirl to cut the hair of steel,
还给了她一套新衣服之后
and gave her a new suit to boot.
但是她们的对头却是莉莉安·卢瑟
But their next adversary is Lillian Luthor herself,
超女与莉娜·卢瑟作证指控莉莉安·卢瑟
这一次  她们的战场是法庭
and this time, their battleground is a courtroom.
情感迸发  跌宕起伏
Emotions. Drama.
家族恩仇
她们是否能够幸存下来
Will they persevere?
捣蛋鬼  你能认真点吗
Mxy, can you please take this seriously?
认真点  因为每一个派对都得有个扫兴鬼
Take it seriously, because every party needs a pooper,
所以我们邀请了卡拉
and that's why we invited Kara.
真的吗
Really?
如果我们要玩搞笑的  干什么不动真格
If we're gonna take the fun out of stuff, let's really do it.
还有超女的真名是什么
And what is Supergirl's real name?
我根本搞不懂这有什么意义
I hardly see how that's relevant.
公民需要知道逮捕他们的
Citizens have the right to know the name
警官的名字
of the officer that arrests them.
如果超女要做法官与陪审团
If Supergirl is gonna act like judge and jury,
我们也应该知道她的名字
we should know her name as well.
按第五修正案  我拒绝回答
I plead the Fifth.
今天莉莉安·卢瑟审判庭上出现强力证词
Powerful testimonies in the trial of Lillian Luthor today.
但是他们会被莉娜·卢瑟拒绝提供
But will they be undercut by Lena Luthor's refusal
超女真实身份的行为削弱吗
to give up Supergirl's identity?
这项人的法则太渺小了
Well, nothing so trifling as the laws of man
居然要阻挡超女
could stand in the way of Supergirl
与莉娜·卢瑟神圣胜利
and Lena Luthor's divine victories!
神
我曾经认为
Where I once thought
真正的力量是行走于我们之中的氪星人
that true power was the Kryptonian walking amongst us,
但是那力量完全比不上
but that power is nothing compared to the might
与一名卢瑟搭档的氪星人
of a Kryptonian paired with a Luthor!
这真是不可思议
This is incredible.
上次莉莉安上法庭时
The last time Lillian was on trial,
整个世界都认为莉娜与她共谋
the whole world suspected Lena of working with her,
但有了超女作为搭档
but having Supergirl as a partner...
这赋予了莉娜的姓氏所没有的信用
...it gives Lena the credibility her last name never could.
-就是这个  -棒
- This is it. - Yes.
这就是我完全没伤害莉娜的时间线
This is the timeline where I truly do no harm to Lena,
而这个世界认为她是个真正的英雄
and the world sees her for the hero she really is.
当然  我相当乐意捐助
Of course, I'm more than happy to donate.
好的
Okay.
-卢瑟女士  -不好
- Miss Luthor. - Oh, no.
那是洛克伍德吗
Is that Lockwood?
你认识我父亲  彼得·洛克伍德
You knew my father, Pete Lockwood?
你是本
You're Ben.
我们外包给他的钢铁工厂
We were sourcing our steel from his factory,
但是他突然关闭了
and then he abruptly closed it.
不是  他没关闭  他给改造成教堂了
No, he didn't close it. He converted it to a church.
拉奥神教
The Cult of Rao.
真抱歉  本
I'm so sorry, Ben.
如果超女和我能帮上你父亲
If Supergirl and I can do anything to help your father--
你不能
You can't.
因为他死了
Because he's dead.
我的父亲  我的妻子
My father, my wife,
我唯一的儿子  乔治  他们跳楼了
my only son, George, they jumped off a roof
因为他们相信
because they believed...
她可以拯救他们
that she would save them.
然而她没有
And she didn't.
真对不起  本
I'm so sorry, Ben.
如果有任何事我们能帮上忙的...
If there's anything I could do to help--
你可以告诉我超女是谁
Well, you could tell me who Supergirl is.
她像个神一样四处招摇
She parades around as a god,
但是却作为人类躲藏在世间
but she hides in plain sight as a human.
卢瑟女士  如果人们知道她是谁
Miss Luthor, if... if people knew who she was,
如果他们知道她今天早上给人带了咖啡
if they knew that she bought a coffee in the morning
或是她坐了公交车
or that she rode the bus
或者是她像我们一样有个工作
or that she worked a job just like the rest of us,
那他们将会停止崇拜她
then they would stop worshipping her.
所以我需要知道她是谁
So, I have to know who she is.
而你将会告诉我
And you are going to tell me.
这绝不可能
It's never gonna happen.
如果你对拉奥神教有意见
And if you have issues with the Cult of Rao,
我建议你去跟克维尔提
I suggest you take it up with Coville.
我已经提过了
I already have.
好呀
Hiya!
托马斯·克维尔想让你相信
Thomas Coville wants you to believe
纳欣诺市的氪星人
that National City's resident Kryptonian
是值得崇拜的  值得为其牺牲的
is someone worth worshipping, worth dying for.
超女是神吗
Is Supergirl a god?
我可不太确定
I'm not sure about that.
不太确定
Not sure about that.
当她晚上回到家
When she goes home at night,
你知道她私下过着人类生活吗
did you know that she lives a secret human life?
直到今天
Until today.
直到今天  因为今天
Until today, because today,
超女将会向全世界揭露她的身份
Supergirl will reveal her identity to the world,
不然  克维尔与卢瑟女士
or... Coville and Miss Luthor will die.
不  超女  不要
No. Supergirl, don't do it!
所以  超女  只剩一小时的氧气了
So, Supergirl, one hour of breathable oxygen left,
计时现在开始
the clock starts now.
-你要怎么办  -别剧透
- What're you gonna do? - Uh... No spoilers.
我太喜欢了  我是说
I'm loving this. Uh, I mean...
我无法承受这悲惨的一幕
I can't trace the signal.
一个单干的人不可能有资源
Look, some lone wolf shouldn't have the resources
来阻挠我们的追踪
to thwart our trackers.
他肯定有强大的帮手
He must have powerful help.
是的  帮手就是莱克斯
Yeah, help spelled L-E-X.
如果是这样  那我们就再也找不到她了
If that's the case, then we are never gonna find her.
待在这里  我来搞定
Stay here, I got it.
我每天早上醒来的时候
Every morning when I wake up...
都在想象这个时刻
I imagine this moment.
超女的身份害死了我爱的人
The moment where being Supergirl gets someone I love killed.
我已经减轻了很多这种恐惧
And I have push that fear so far down...
不然我都没法起床
...or I... I can't get out of bed.
但现在它来了
But now, here it is.
我最大的恐惧就在我面前
My greatest fear, just staring me right in the face.
我得救莉娜
I have to save Lena.
我得去  但如果我告诉这个世界我是谁
I... I have to, but if I tell the world who I am,
那我会让其他我爱的人都陷入更大的危险
then I put everyone else I love at even greater risk.
艾丽克斯  荣恩  詹姆斯  你
Alex, J'onn, James, you.
要是你们谁受伤了怎么办
What if one of you gets hurt?
不要担心我们  好吗
Don't worry about the rest of us, okay?
我们不会有事的
We're gonna be fine.
不  莉娜现在需要你的帮助
No, Lena is the one that needs your help right now.
我们可以照顾好自己
We can take care of ourselves...
因为你教过我们方法了
because you taught us how.
我们正在纳欣诺市政厅
We're here at National City Hall,
超女随时都会到
where Supergirl is set to arrive any minute,
她会向全世界宣布她的人类身份
and announce her human identity to the world.
-对不起  -天啊  你好强壮
- Oh, sorry. - Jeez. You're strong.
大家好
Hello.
我是卡拉·丹弗斯
I am Kara Danvers.
你们有人可能知道我是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
Some of you may know me as a reporter for CatCo Worldwide Media.
但我也是
But I am also...
来自氪星的卡拉·佐·艾尔
Kara Zor-El, of Krypton.
我就是超女
I am Supergirl.
太好了  哥们
Good stuff, my dude!
但我们还是该杀了人质  对吧
But we should kill the hostages anyway, right?
不
No.
不  我们信守承诺
No, we keep our word.
把地址发给他们
Send them the location.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
好好呼吸  莉娜  没事了
Just breathe, Lena. It's okay.
也许是时候让世界知道了
Maybe it's time the world knows.
我一直不敢向世人透露我的身份
I've always been so afraid to reveal my identity to the world,
但你看  我救了莉娜
but look, it saved Lena.
也许...
Maybe...
只是也许...
Just maybe, this...
这就是该选择的时间线  让我们...
this is the timeline to stick with. Let's...
我理解你为什么这么想
I see why you would think that,
但也许我们应该直接跳到结局
but, um, maybe we should skip ahead to the ending?
不  怎么了
Oh, no, what happens?
超女的身份公开后
After Supergirl's identity was released to the world,
自由代表和他的追随者们准备袭击
Agent Liberty and his followers targeted
超女的每个朋友
each of Supergirl's friends,
包括她的前雇主凯特·格兰特
including her former employer Cat Grant...
不
No.
一个接一个  没有幸存者
...one by one. There were no survivors.
艾丽克斯·丹弗斯  温·肖特  荣恩·荣兹
Alex Danvers, Winn Schott... J'onn J'onzz...
好了  好了  够了  停下
All right, all right, enough. Stop.
我不想再看了
I don't wanna see anymore.
请把它关掉
Please turn it off, please.
我什么时候告诉莉娜真相都无所谓
It doesn't matter when I tell Lena the truth.
总会让事情变得更糟
It always makes things worse.
我觉得我太害怕去承认
I think I've been too scared to admit it to myself, but...
如果莉娜和我不是朋友的话  她会过得更好
I think Lena would be better off if she and I were never friends.
这是你想看到的世界吗
Is that the world you wanna see?
不是
No.
无论怎样  请让我看看
Please just show me anyway.
发生什么了
What happened?
我们在哪
Where are we?
你的阁楼之前在的地方
Where your loft used to be.
你知道吗  不了  谢谢
You know what? No thanks.
-不  我不需要看到这个  -好的
- Nope. I don't need to see it. - Yeah.
-你能带我们离开这里吗  -好的  乐意效劳
- Can you just snap us out of here? - Yep. With pleasure.
怎么回事
What's happening?
我完全感觉不到第五维度
I can't feel the Fifth Dimension at all.
我的超能力没了
Without my powers...
我们被困在这了吗
We're stuck here?
-我们应该离开这里  -你觉得呢
- We should get out of here. - You think?
市民们  你们在宵禁后出门  违反了卢瑟法
Citizens, you're out after curfew, in defiance of Luthor Law.
这个世界糟透了
This world sucks!
你还不知道另一半
You don't know the half of it.
看看我找到了谁
Look who I found.
卡拉  谢天谢地你来了
Oh, Kara, thank God you're here.
这是谁
Who's this?
这是我朋友  捣蛋鬼先生
Oh, this is my friend, Mr. Mxyzptlk.
-捣蛋鬼先生  -是的
- Mr. Mxyzptlk? - Yeah.
你以为换了张新脸
What, you thought with the new face,
我们就认不出你了吗
we wouldn't recognize the same old you?
这就是那个想娶卡拉的人
This is the guy who tried to make Kara marry him.
没事  蒙·艾尔  因为他改过了
It's fine, Mon-El. Because he is reformed...
他其实在帮我
and he's actually helping me.
不  你知道吗  蒙·艾尔是对的  好吗
Uh, no... You know what? No, Mon-El is right. Okay?
我太卑劣了  去追求一个
It was despicable of me to pursue a woman
从一开始就对我不感兴趣的女人
who so clearly was not interested in me from the get-go.
我曲解了那个房间的含义  我会变得更好的
I misread the room, and I'm gonna be better.
当捣蛋鬼很难
It's tough to be an imp.
接下来的日子我会努力的
And I'm gonna try for the rest of my days.
也许我们可以让过去成为过去  是吧
So, maybe we can let the past be the past, huh?
来吧
Come on.
好吧  你赢了
Okay, you won.
-我们需要尽可能多的帮助  -好的
- We'll need all the help we can get. - All right, well,
听着  事情并不是那样的  我会解释的  但
look... things are not as they seem, and I will explain, but...
首先  有人能告诉我这里发生了什么吗
First, will someone please tell me what's going on here?
纳欣诺市的人们
People of National City,
我很遗憾地通知你们  被称为超女的恐怖分子
I regret to inform you that the terrorist known
-正在逍遥法外  -恐怖分子
- as Supergirl is at large. - Terrorist?
她和一个第五维度的生物在一起
She's working with a Fifth Dimensional being,
有能力造成大规模破坏
capable of mass destruction.
为了保护你们  霍普机器人
H.O.P.E. Robots have been deployed
已经在整个城市部署了
throughout the city for your protection.
请向他们报告任何可疑的活动
Please, report to them any and all suspicious activity.
记住...
And remember...
我的目标一如既往地是
My goal is, as it has always been...
保护你们不受伤害
to protect you from harm.
不
No.
莉娜第一次来纳欣诺市
When Lena first came to National City...
接手L公司的时候
to take over L-Corp,
莱克斯想暗杀她
Lex tried to have her assassinated.
他失败了
He failed,
但她在袭击中受了重伤
but she was seriously injured in the attack.
她失踪了两年
She disappeared for two years.
等她回来的时候  每个人都说她不一样了
When she came back, everybody said that she was different,
她变了
that she had changed.
创伤  孤独
The trauma, the loneliness...
把她逼疯了
it drove her mad.
她报复莱克斯  杀了他
She retaliated against Lex, killed him.
让半个纳欣诺市跟随她
Took half of National City along with her.
现在她用铁腕统治着剩下的一切
Now, she rules what's left with an iron fist.
-主宰是她的执法者  -布莱尼也是
- Reign is her enforcer. - And Brainy, too.
她抓住了他  招降了他
She captured him. Aligned him.
现在他没有感情
Now, he has no emotions...
-只会做莉娜让他做的事  -不
- and does whatever Lena tells him to. - Oh, no.
这...  我犯了一个严重的错误
This, this... I have made a terrible mistake.
这个世界是我的责任
This world is my responsibility.
好吧  我们还是可以解决的
Okay. Okay, we can still fix this.
我需要我的超能力  但自从我们来到这里
I need my powers. But since we've been here...
超能力就不见了
They've disappeared.
肯定是因为
That must be because
莉娜利用了五维能量
Lena tapped into the Fifth Dimensional energy
给她的警用机器人供电
to use it to power her police robots.
只要她在利用五维能量
And as long as she's harnessing the Fifth Dimension,
你就没有超能力
then you can't access it.
在莉娜找到我之前  我在L公司工作了两年
I worked at L-Corp for about two years before Lena found me out.
我们抓到一个罪犯
Uh, we caught a criminal.
他没有名字  但他戴了一顶帽子
He didn't have a name, but he had a hat
什么都能从里面变出来
that he could pull anything out of.
那是我的老伙计
Old drinking buddy of mine.
我有次打扑克把那顶帽子输给了他
I lost that hat to him in a poker game.
那顶帽子具有很多五维魔法
That hat contains a lot of Fifth Dimensional magic.
所以只要我们给你弄到那顶帽子...
So, if we get you the hat...
给我帽子  我可以让这一切...
Get me the hat, I can make all of this go...
消失
Bye-bye.
要么投降  要么去死
Surrender the imp or die!
拿到那顶帽子
Get the hat!
我们会拖住她的
We'll hold her off!
来吧  我给你带路
Come on, I'll show you the way!
我帮你断后
And I've got your back!
布莱尼  是我
Brainy, it's me.
是尼娅
It's Nia.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
我知道我不必
I know I don't have to.
但我觉得我会享受这个过程
But I think I will enjoy it.
去找莉娜  我来阻止主宰
Go to Lena, I've got Reign.
莉娜
Lena?
是我
It's me.
是超女
It's Supergirl.
是卡拉
It's Kara.
卡拉是谁
Who's Kara?
只是个朋友而已
Just a friend.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
并不真正了解
Not really.
但你和我想要的一样
But you and I want the same thing...
不伤害别人
to do no harm.
超女想要一个没有伤害的世界
Supergirl wants a world without harm.
真好笑
That's rich.
我哥哥把我的直升机击落时  你在哪里
Where were you when my brother blew my helicopter out of the sky?
我母亲把我伤痕累累的身体拖回实验室
When my mother dragged my broken body to a laboratory
不为我疗伤  反而拿我做实验
and experimented on me instead of fixing me?
当这个世界支离破碎时  你又在哪里
Where were you when this world was ripped apart by the seams?
你在哪里
Where were you?
我很抱歉重要的时候我不在
I'm sorry I wasn't there when it mattered.
我也很抱歉
So am I.
帽子就在这个房间里  我能感觉到
The hat's in this room. I can feel it.
是荣恩
It's J'onn.
-他需要我们的帮助  -不  他需要这个
- He needs our help. - No, he needs this.
该面对正义审判了  火星猎人
Time to face justice, Manhunter.
荣恩  接着
J'onn! Catch!
梦想者  现在就行动
Dreamer, do it now!
你对疼痛一无所知
You don't know the first thing about pain.
但我了解
But I do.
我可以向你展示  让你感受到我的感受
I can show you, make you feel what I feel.
我不会跟你动手的  莉娜
I won't fight you, Lena.
那么你会尖叫着死去
Then you'll die screaming.
找到了
Found it.
我们回家了
We're home.
我的天啊
Holy cow!
刚才是我一生中最让人心力交瘁的经历
That was the most emotionally draining experience of my life,
要知道  我也是经历过磨难的人
and let me tell ya, I've had some doozies.
好了  一切尚未结束
Okay. So, it ain't over till it's over.
我们得找个时间
So, now, we've gotta find a time
让你回去告诉莉娜真相
for you to go back and tell Lena the truth.
-准备好再试一次了吗  -不要
You ready for one more go? No.
不  坚决不要
No. Absolutely not!
我现在意识到  我何时告诉莉娜真相并不重要
I realize now that it doesn't matter when I tell Lena the truth.
总会有后果的
There will always be consequences.
严重的后果
Huge ones.
如果我不能回去把我的错误一笔勾销
And if I can't go back and snap my mistakes away,
那我就只能接受这些错误了
I'm just gonna have to live with them.
天呐
Oh, boy.
好吧
Okay.
我知道结果和我们预想的不一样  但你...
I know it didn't turn out the way we expected, but you...
你还是帮了我  捣蛋鬼
You still helped me, Mxy.
你让我从内疚的负担中解脱出来
You freed me from my burden of guilt, so...
去吧  你自由了
Go, be free.
用你的魔法去做任何你想做的事
Use your magic to do whatever it is you do.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我得说
And I should say, uh...
在我遇见你之前  我...
Before I met you, I was, um...
我很孤独
I was pretty lonely.
在那种痛苦中  我...
You know, and in that pain, I...
我会强迫别人...
I would tend to sort of, force myself...
去接受我
on people, and, uh...
今天和你们在一起
Out there with you today,
拯救世界  我觉得...
saving the world, I felt like, um...
我觉得有人喜欢我  因为我就是我
I felt like I was liked, for being me.
我觉得我也有朋友
I felt like I had friends.
另外
And, uh...
你说的是真的  卡拉
it's true what you said, Kara.
那种魔法
That magic...
不能被强施于人
can't be forced.
它必须被找到
It has to be found.
我为你骄傲  捣蛋鬼
I'm proud of you, Mxy.
谢谢你所做的一切
Thanks for everything.
不客气
You're welcome.
如果你不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要去八十年代的狂欢节了
I'm off to Mardi Gras in the '80s.
十八世纪八十年代
The 1780s.
莉娜决定与莱克斯合作
让我猜猜
Let me guess...
你是再次来告诉我  我应该原谅你
You're here to tell me once again that I should forgive you.
或者我不应该和我哥哥合作
Or maybe that I shouldn't work with my brother?
这次不是
Not this time.
我承认我犯了一个错误
I recognize I made a mistake
长久以来对你隐瞒了我的身份
in hiding my identity from you for so long,
但过去的已经过去  我无法改变
but the past is the past, and I can't change it.
是否原谅我  那是你的选择
Forgive me or not, that's your choice.
就像你选择和莱克斯合作一样
Just like it's your choice to work with Lex.
我不再为你的错误决定而自责了
I'm done blaming myself for your bad decisions.
那你为什么来找我
Then why are you here?
告诉你从现在开始
To tell you that from now on,
你要对自己的行为负责
you're accountable for your own actions.
如果你决定原谅我  我会在你身边
If you decide to forgive me, I will be there for you.
但如果你继续和莱克斯合作...
But if you continue to work with Lex...
如果你们俩要将自己的计划
If you go through with whatever it is
贯彻到底
the two of you are planning,
我会尽我所能阻止你
I will do everything in my power to stop you...
就像我对待其他恶棍一样
just like I would any other villain.
好多吃的啊
This is an extraordinary amount of food.
是捣蛋鬼送的离别礼物
A parting gift from Mxy.
我们应该多请捣蛋鬼过来
Well, I think we should have Mxy here more often.
我听说五维干预
I hear Fifth Dimensional interventions
能神奇地改变一个人的看法
do wonders for one's perspective.
你知道吗
You know what?
这是真的
Actually, they really do.
看到现实的不同版本  让我意识到
Seeing all those alternate versions of reality made me realize,
事后批评自己没有任何好处
second-guessing myself doesn't do any good.
是的
No.
所以  如果我犯了错  我必须往前看
So, if I make a mistake, I just have to move on.
为什么要笑
What is that smile?
你们几个啊
You guys.
伙计们  自从我成为超女的那刻起
Guys, you've been with me from...
你们就一直陪着我
the second I became Supergirl.
无论巅峰  还是低谷
In my best moments and especially my worst moments.
这对我而言意义重大
That means the world to me.
我也是
Sames.
都一样
Back at you.
聚则强
El-may-arah.
"Stronger together."
-说法不同  -本质相同
- Potato. - Po-tah-to.